[{"question": "  would you like some more coffee, baby-doll?", "answer": " i'm fine, thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  yeah, see, i can't pull of baby-doll can i?", "answer": " no. i think we learned that from the sugarlips incident. i'm gonna get some tea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hiya doin' pumpkin?", "answer": " nope.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " so it looks like it's going really well for you two, huh?", "answer": " i know, really well. in fact, i'm gonna ask phoebe to move in with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  oh my god!", "answer": " what do you, what do you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i think that is so great! when are you gonna ask her?", "answer": " tonight, but don't say anything. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i swear, i promise. i promise. oh my god, i'm so excited! {and i just can't hide it! i'm about to lose control and i think i like it! sorry, just couldn't resist it.} all right, listen let me tell you, do not get her flowers. okay? because y'know, she cries when they die, and there's the whole funeral\u009a", "answer": "  i'll see you after work sweetie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " so, what movie should we see?", "answer": "  gary's gonna ask you to move in with him!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what?! really?!", "answer": " he just told me at the counter. he made me promise not to tell, but i couldn't hold it in any longer!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i can't believe this!", "answer": "  right, because it's fast. because, it's so fast. it's fast!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " relax! it's phoebe! not you!", "answer": " oh! good for you pheebs, way to go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no, but it is fast. isn't it?", "answer": " ohhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " no, i like him a lot but i don't think i'm ready for this!", "answer": " so, what are you gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " i don't know. i'll just handle it\u0097i'll ask you to talk to him!", "answer": " me?! why me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " because you are so afraid of commitment! you talk to him, make him scared like you! make him a\u009aman!", "answer": " i'll try, but i'm not sure what good it would do, y'know? because i'm a lot less afraid of commitment than i used to be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hey ross, is uh, is staten island really an island?", "answer": " uh-huh, that's why they call it staten island.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ohhh. i thought it was like long island.", "answer": "  also an island.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey, what time is it?", "answer": "  2:17.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " wow! you realize that we've been throwing this ball, without dropping it, for like an hour?", "answer": " are you serious?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah. i realized it about a half-hour ago but i didn't want to say anything 'cause i didn't want to jinx it.", "answer": " wow! we are pretty good at this! hey! we totally forgot about lunch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, i-i, i think that's the first time i ever missed a meal!  yeah, my pants are a little loose!", "answer": "  hey, you guys\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " is monica here? joey and ross: no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " all right listen umm, i just bought something i'm not sure she's gonna like it, and it's gonna seem a little crazy, but this is something that i wanted since i was a little girl.", "answer": " you bought shawn cassidy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " noo! i wish! okay, you ready? joey and ross: yeah!", "answer": " okay!  check it out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " what-what is it?!", "answer": " what the hell is that?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " it's a, it's a cat!", "answer": " that, is not a cat! {i have to agree with joey on this one.}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yes it is!", "answer": " why is it inside out?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " excuse me! but this is a purebred, show-quality sphinx cat!", "answer": " how much did you pay for that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " well, it was a little extravagant, but i a pretty good deal.", "answer": " yeah? how much?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " a thousand bucks.", "answer": " on a cat??!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " it's not a cat!", "answer": " all right listen ball boys! my grandmother had one of these when i was a little girl and it was the sweetest thing! i mean it was so cute, it would sit in my lap and purr all day long, and i would drag a shoestring on the ground and he would chase it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " free cats do that too, y'know. {which reminds me, if i might get a little political here, support your local animal shelter. pet shops are not the place to buy dogs and cats from, you get a much better deal from the shelter, plus they probably won't die on you in a week and a half. if you want a leash, go to the pet shop. if you want the dog for that leash, go to the shelter and save it's life. now back to regularly scheduled programming.}", "answer": " it's not a cat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  hey, you wanna get something to eat or uh, do you wanna see how long we can throw this ball back and forth? huh?", "answer": " uhh, the ball thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " hey ross, wouldn't it be great if we could go two straight hours without dropping it?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " uhh, yeah it would! let's do it!", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  uh-oh.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " man, i didn't think we were gonna make it!", "answer": " i know!  don't switch hands, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hey chandler, what are you doing here?", "answer": " gary, i'm here to report a crime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " it is a crime that you and i don't spend more time together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  what's up?", "answer": " well, i heard that you thinking about asking phoebe to move in with you and i thought maybe, we should have a talk. man to uh, me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " sure. okay.", "answer": " uh, are you crazy? are you insane? if you live with phoebe, you two are gonna be y'know, live-living together!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " yeah, i-i considered that. i just know it would make me happy.", "answer": " you mean scared.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " no, i mean happy.", "answer": " scared? happy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " chandler, what-what are you doing?", "answer": " i am trying to open your eyes, my man! don't you see, if you lived with phoebe she's always gonna be there. you're gonna get home, she's there. you go to bed, she's there. you wake up and oh yes, she's there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i know! i can't wait!", "answer": " were you're parents happy, or something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " listen chandler, the way i see it is that i was lucky enough to find someone that i really love. i just\u0097i wanna be around her as much as i can.", "answer": " wow, y'know when you say it, it doesn't sound so scary.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " so you know what i'm talking about, right?", "answer": " yeah, i think i do! y'know what? you move in with her! you move in with her right now! maybe i should in with monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " no, it's too soon for you guys.", "answer": "  yeah, you're right about that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " \u009anow when they found the remains of the mesozoic mastodon they discovered what appeared to be the remains of a paleozoic amphibian in its jaws! how did it get there?! {y'know, sometimes i think the script writers through in a line like that to try to trip me up. but it won't work. i'll always have the last laugh! okay, so maybe i'm a little deluded, it's probably just my spellchecker. but, i must admit i did get mesozoic and paleozoic on the first attempt. yay me! anyhoo\u009a}", "answer": " maybe this should be more of a quiet game. {oh, all right! geez, i can't have any fun!}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  hey guys!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " joey, i left my watch on the counter last night.  it was right here, where is it?", "answer": " i don't know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " all right, come on, i'm-i'm late for work!", "answer": " how do you know? you don't have a watch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " guys, could you please just stop throwing the ball for one minute and just help me find it!", "answer": " oh, i don't know\u009a. yeah, can't do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " monica, whatever you do, do not drop that ball!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " 2 hours, 27 minutes.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey rach!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " check it out! almost 3 hours without droppin' it!", "answer": " oh, wow! congratulations, that's quite a waste of time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " rach?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well, it's my cat.", "answer": "  what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh yeah, i got a cat.", "answer": " i don't want a cat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " oh, don't worry, it's not a cat.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " you guys this cat is nothing like my grandmother's cat. i mean, it's not sweet, it's not cute, i even dragged that little string on the ground, and it just flipped out and scratched the hell out of me. and i swear, i know this sounds crazy, but every time this cat hisses at me i know it's saying, \"rachel!\"", "answer": " doesn't sound as crazy as paying a thousand dollars for a cat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  what?! you paid a thousand dollars for a cat when you owe me 300!!", "answer": " well, i was gonna let you play with it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hmm, did you talk to gary about the moving in thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " yes i did, and i think you should do it.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " he's a great guy, y'know? and he loves you a lot, you are a very lucky lady.", "answer": " you are useless! freaking out about commitment is the one thing you can do! the one thing! and you can't even do that right! god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry.  if you ask me, i'd move in with him.", "answer": " ohh!! god!  ooh!  get out of here, good for nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hey chandler.", "answer": " hey gar!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  hi sweetie.  hi, can i talk to you for a second?", "answer": " yeah! okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " you look very pretty today.", "answer": " thanks! okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " here's the thing.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " y'know i really want to move this relationship forward.", "answer": " uh-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " because if you're not moving forward, y'know you're just moving backwards.", "answer": " no that's not true. if you're not moving forward, you're just staying still. and staying still is good. watch this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " phoebe?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i want you to move in with me.", "answer": " that is so sweet. but don't you think it's a little too soon? i mean there's so much we don't know about each other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  oh. oh-oh-okay, i get it.", "answer": " i just\u0097i don't want us to jump into something we're not ready for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  uh-huh.", "answer": " i really don't want to mess up what we have. i'm just\u0097i'm worried it's gonna be a big mistake.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  yeah.", "answer": " which is why my answer is yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  really?!", "answer": " uh-huh!  i'm so\u009ahappy.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  monica! stop throwing it so hard! we're on the same team!", "answer": " four hours? you guys have been doing this for four hours?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " that's right baby.", "answer": " all right, let me in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  no-no! don't do it! don't!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " he's a dropper!", "answer": " oh yeah, that's right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " i'm not a dropper!", "answer": " it's really a uh-uh three person game, y'know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " it's throwing and catching!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " whoa-whoa you guys, it's not a cat!", "answer": " oh my\u0097oh good god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  i give up you guys, i don't know what i'm going to do with this thing!", "answer": " baking it didn't help, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " so, why don't you just take it back to where you got it?", "answer": " i tried! they won't take her back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " maybe that's because she's a minion of the anti-christ.", "answer": " rach, why won't they take it back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " well, they said would but they would only give me store credit. i mean, what am i going to do, get a thousand regular cats?", "answer": " look, if you want you can keep it at our place until you find out what to do with it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh my god, the cat's made my eyes water! don't-don't throw it to me! my vision's been compromised!!  oh god! okay. okay. it's okay. man, that was close.", "answer": " yeah, you almost overreacted to something. phoebe and gary:  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " we have great news!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " we're moving in together! isn't it great! yay!", "answer": " congratulations! congrats!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " i know, i'm so excited!", "answer": " so am i!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " well, you're not more excited than i am! no way! i'm the most excited!", "answer": " okay, i'll see you at the station later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " okay, yeah, i'll see you later! don't forget about the moving in!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " so you're moving in with him. what happened?", "answer": " i couldn't tell him no. he got so sad. maybe it'll be all right. i do really like him a lot and probably do it eventually anyway and plus, think of all the money i'll save on stamps.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " why, do you write him a lot?", "answer": " no, i just heard when people live together, they split the cost of stamps. don't they?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " hey, honey! okay, so did you find any apartments? anything in brooklyn heights?", "answer": " no, nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh really?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " nothing at all?", "answer": " no, as soon as something opens up we'll move right in. unless it doesn't have a pool, i need a pool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " phoebe, can i talk to you for a second?", "answer": " uh-huh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  yeah, i feel great. 'cause we're moving in together.", "answer": " so you uh, you checked the paper for listings in brooklyn heights, right? you-you checked the post?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " yeah, uh-huh, there was nothing.  can i get some water?", "answer": " in a minute. you-you checked today's post?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " umm, yeah! today's.", "answer": " 'cause uh, this is today's post  and uh, these are the listings i found.  brooklyn heights, two bedroom.  brooklyn heights, one bedroom.  brooklyn heights,  brooklyn heights,  brooklyn heights!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  are these for rent! i thought people were just bragging!", "answer": " let me tell you what i think might be going on.  no-no-no, don't look at the table. look at me.  okay, i think somebody asked someone to move in with them. and i think someone said, \"yes\" but now she's having doubts because things are moving to fast for someone. does that sound at all possible to you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " phoebe\u009a", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " phoebe, it's okay that you feel this way. i mean it is soon. and there's a lot of things we don't know about each other, and i just figure that everything i really like. and the things i don't know, i get to learn about at someplace with both our names on the mailbox.", "answer": " that's so sweet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " sweethart, but none of that matters if it's too soon for you. it's fine! we don't have to move in together. i just\u0097i want you to be happy", "answer": " living with you would make me happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " phoebe, you don't have to say that.", "answer": " no, i really wanna live with you! i wanna move in with you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " yes. definitely! yes! let's live in an apartment that we both live in!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " oh that's great!", "answer": " oh wait, one sec. one sec.  hey you! behind the glass! who are you looking at! i've always wanted to say that when i was in one of these rooms,  which was never!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " show cat! quality show cat! show cat!  woman no. 1:  oh my god! what's wrong with your baby?!", "answer": " it's not a baby! it's a cat! woman no. 1: eew! it's creepy looking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " oh no! no! it's actually\u0097it's very sweet. it's very sweet. look!  yeah, do you want it? woman no. 1:  no, i hate cats.", "answer": " well, so then what are you doing to me? okay? just get out of here! all right? move on!  woman no. 2: wow! what an unusual cat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " yes! thank you! exactly! you want it? woman no. 2: maybe. i was thinking about getting a cat, i was just going to go to the shelter  but\u009a okay, why not?", "answer": " oh, terrific! that'll be $2,000. woman no. 2: what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " okay, a thousand. woman no. 2: i thought you wanted to adopt your cat.", "answer": " well, i do, but you're just gonna have to actually look at this as more of an investment than a cat. woman no. 2: okay, yeah, i just wanted a cat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " i'm starving!", "answer": " come on guys! suck it up! we're closing in on ten hours! it's gut-check time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " i don't know who made you the boss? all right? we  invented this game!", "answer": " please! i made this game what it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " not fun anymore?", "answer": " i'm still hungry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " all right, there's some pizza at my place, we can all eat with one hand right? are you with me?", "answer": " i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " rachel! what is your cat doing in one of my bowls!", "answer": " it's not! i'm defrosting a chicken.  oh, i uh sold mrs. whiskerson.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " oh, thank god!", "answer": " did you get your money back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " yeah, 15 hundred dollars.", "answer": " wow! you made a profit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": "  i just came for the red-velvet pillow.", "answer": " oh yeah, there you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " thanks rachel. and-and don't forget you-you can come visit her anytime you want.", "answer": " oh good, great! i'll-i'll keep that in mind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " i really like waking up with you.", "answer": " i like waking up with you too.  oh! it's such a beautiful morning.  oh, i can stay here all day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " that would be great!", "answer": " we could have breakfast in bed\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " wait, just a second.", "answer": " okay.  oh! oh no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " all right! come on monica! look alive! come on, look alive!", "answer": "  oh good, you're all up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " phoebe! it's 6 o'clock in the morning! why aren't you at gary's?", "answer": " oh yeah, that's over.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " come on! gary's such a great guy! whatever the problem is, you can work it out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " he shot a bird!", "answer": " oh that is over!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " that's terrible! i'm sorry!", "answer": " phoebe, are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " yeah. yeah, i'll be alright.", "answer": " oh hey, here pheebs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " it's okay. it's okay. just pretend that it didn't happen! okay? no one needs to know! i mean, phoebe's not an official ballplayer! i mean, only official ballplayers can drop the ball!", "answer": " all right. okay. i'm starving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " phoebe, honey, wanna get some breakfast?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " you guys wanna eat here?", "answer": " yeah! as long as we're here! ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " man that was great! huh? can you believe how long we threw that ball around?", "answer": " yeah, it is amazing it lasted that long.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": " i know. my arm is killing me.", "answer": " no, i meant with the dropper over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}]